[
    {
        "qid": 446362,
        "question": "Patient is a 73 year old female.<br>- The patient has been coughing up blood.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain in the posterior chest wall on both the right and left sides.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing significant shortness of breath or difficulty breathing.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient is a former smoker.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Epiglottitis",
        "option2": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "45%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 993458,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest and the posterior chest wall on the right side.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Influenza",
        "option4": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 822028,
        "question": "Patient is a 36 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive, burning, and scary.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest, hypochondrium (left), and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, then goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently thrown up blood or something resembling coffee beans.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Localized edema",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 428285,
        "question": "Patient is a 42 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Bronchospasm / acute asthma exacerbation",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 788539,
        "question": "Patient is a 76 year old female.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height as them.<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient thinks they are pregnant or are currently pregnant.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Acute pulmonary edema",
        "option2": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 511235,
        "question": "Patient is a 19 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Cluster headache",
        "option2": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option3": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option4": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 314621,
        "question": "Patient is a 15 year old female.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient has family members who have been diagnosed with anemia.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient has very abundant or very long menstruation periods.<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient has noticed light red blood or blood clots in their stool.<br>- The patient has traveled to Asia in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option2": "Acute pulmonary edema",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Unstable angina",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "64%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1156580,
        "question": "Patient is a 54 year old male.<br>- The patient has been coughing up blood.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has experienced an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.<br>- The patient is a former smoker.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.<br>- The patient has family members who have had lung cancer.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option3": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "85%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1049152,
        "question": "Patient is a 36 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right cheek, left cheek, and left temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1057572,
        "question": "Patient is a 50 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tugging and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the belly and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest and upper chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has asthma or has had to use a bronchodilator in the past.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option3": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option4": "Cluster headache",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "72%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1009353,
        "question": "Patient is a 4 year old male.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the left side of the chest.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Myasthenia gravis",
        "option2": "Myocarditis",
        "option3": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 103892,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option2": "Localized edema",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "83%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 673249,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old female.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has felt like they were suffocating for a very short time, associated with an inability to breathe or speak.<br>- The patient has been treated in hospital recently for nausea, agitation, intoxication, or aggressive behavior and received medication via an intravenous or intramuscular route.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Laryngospasm",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "64%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1012248,
        "question": "Patient is a 25 year old female.<br>- The patient has started or taken antipsychotic medication within the last 7 days.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has felt like they were suffocating for a very short time, associated with an inability to breathe or speak.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient has a hard time opening or raising one or both eyelids.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has annoying muscle spasms in their face, neck, or another part of their body.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Influenza",
        "option2": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option3": "Pericarditis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 267119,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old female.<br>- The patient has started or taken antipsychotic medication within the last 7 days.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient has a hard time opening or raising one or both eyelids.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has annoying muscle spasms in their face, neck, or another part of their body.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option2": "Pneumonia",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]